dreamsresorts.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy

### DREAMS RESORTS & SPAS - PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Website you accept our Policy. We may revise it at any time by updating the Website.

### General 

This policy covers how AMRESORTS treats personal information that AMRESORTS collects and receives, including information related to your past use of AMRESORTS products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that AMRESORTS does not own or control or to people that AMRESORTS does not manage or employ. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our web site, dreamsresorts.com. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

### Personal Information 

AMRESORTS will only obtain personal information from you when necessary and when you choose to provide it, such as if you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion; or when you register; or when you sign up for Email specials; or when you request information about various vacation packages we offer; or when you make travel arrangements using our web site; or if you contact AMRESORTS using our web site. If you contact AMRESORTS, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Wherever AMRESORTS collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

Personal information that we may request from you in order to provide you with our product could include your, name, date of birth, address, phone number, Email address, password, credit card number, credit card expiration date, and the amount that is being charged or paid. This personal information is collected when you voluntarily complete the online booking form that requests this information. The information you provide may be used to provide you with a product, collect payment for our product, and/or to allow you access to our online services.

### Account Information & Travel Preferences 

You may choose to register with us and create a personal account. If you create an account, you will allow us to tailor your search results to your own personal interests and preferences. The personal information we collect from you, if you choose to register includes: name, address, Email address, preferred travel agent, password and password reminder. The travel preference information we collect from you includes: departure state, preferred airport, destination/hobby interests, duration of stay preference, price range and seasonal preference. You must create a password to create an account, so your account is password-protected. This is unique and regarded as confidential; consequently, it should be carefully guarded. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords, User IDs, and/or any account information. Our secure server encrypts all personal information so that it cannot be read as it is transmitted over the Internet. You may modify your travel profile and account information at any time by going to My Vacation and updating your travel preferences and or account information.

### Email Communications

AMRESORTS may, from time to time, send you Email messages regarding our product specials and services, only if you have opted-in to receive such messages. Once you have opted-in to receive Email from us, you may choose to opt-out of Email communications at any time by updating your account. Regardless of your communication preferences, even if you have opted-out of Email marketing messages, AMRESORTS.com retains the right to send you a transaction-specific Email confirmation when you have booked a vacation on our website.

### Security 

AMRESORTS has implemented technology and systems that protect the information you provide. In those instances when you are asked to submit private information such as a credit card number, you can be assured that we have security measures in place to protect this information. We protect your information with state-of-the-art Secure Socket Layer (add link to our Certificate with Verisign) SSL Technology. This technology provides the advanced encryption tools necessary to protect information transmitted between your computer and our server. Encryption means that your information is converted into code before it is dispatched over the Internet.

### Use of Cookies 

In order to help us provide you with a more personalized experience, we may send a cookie to your browser. The cookie is a small text file that resides on your hard drive. This cookie will indicate if you are registered or not, your home gateway airport preference if you have registered and your last search values for a gateway and a destination. Most web browsers allow you to exercise control of cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. If you choose to block cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of our website. Consult your web browser documentation for instructions on how to control this function.

### Why does AMRESORTS collect information? 

AMRESORTS' primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our site. This includes customized vacation packages to meet your travel plans, budget and other preferences, interactive communications, and other types of services, which are completely free to you. AMRESORTS may advertise certain hotels, destinations, or excursions. By knowing a little about you, AMRESORTS is able to deliver more relevant advertisements, packages, and vacation plans to you. In this process, the advertiser never has access to your individual information only AMRESORTS has access to this information.

AMRESORTS does research on our user's demographics, interests, and behaviors based upon the information provided to us through our web site. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. AMRESORTS may share this aggregated data with advertisers or business partners.

### Who is collecting information? 

When you are using AMRESORTS site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with AMRESORTS alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than AMRESORTS you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you may choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. Promotions that run on AMRESORTS' web site may be co-sponsored by AMRESORTS and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor or co-sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared. Please be aware that AMRESORTS advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information collections practices of those websites.

### With whom does AMRESORTS share my information? 

AMRESORTS will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. AMRESORTS may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating AMRESORTS Fair Trade Contract or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) AMRESORTS' rights or property, other AMRESORTS' users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. AMRESORTS may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. AMRESORTS does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to participate in certain promotions or contests.

### LEGAL STATEMENT

Policy and guidelines for use of marks in advertising, promotion and display   
AMRESORTS and its affiliates have the exclusive rights to use the AMRESORTS service mark and other AMRESORTS marks and logos. Under the trademark laws, the AMRESORTS companies must prevent the use of their names and marks in ways that could give customers and potential customers the mistaken impression that an AMRESORTS company owns or is affiliated with an agency using its marks. AMRESORTS (and trademark law) allow the "fair use" of AMRESORTS marks and logos by agencies, in a truthful, informational way in accordance with the rules provided here. Please adhere to the following specific rules when using AMRESORTS names and marks in promotions on Internet web sites and in print advertisements.

### General Rules 

All uses of the AMRESORTS name or any AMRESORTS mark must relate solely to AMRESORTS travel packages and not to the agencies selling them. Agencies that sell AMRESORTS packages may not refer to themselves in any context as "AMRESORTS travel agents" or to their businesses as "official AMRESORTS travel agencies."

Travel agencies may only use signage, window displays, or point of purchase items employing the AMRESORTS name or any AMRESORTS mark (a) as provided by AMRESORTS, or (b) as approved in writing by AMRESORTS.

No one may copy any content appearing in any AMRESORTS website, brochure, or advertising without express written permission from AMRESORTS.

AMRESORTS marks should be used with the ® symbol, and the use should be accompanied by a legend appearing at the bottom of the page where used that the mark is registered; for example, AMRESORTS is a registered trademark.

### Internet Web Sites 

No one may use the name AMRESORTS or any AMRESORTS mark (or anything confusingly similar) as part of an Internet domain name.  
No agency may display the AMRESORTS mark by itself on a web site without prior written approval.

Travel agencies may use an AMRESORTS mark in a website in the following ways: a. An AMRESORTS mark may be used as part of a statement such as "We sell AMRESORTS travel packages," so long as all of the words in the sentence are of a similar size. b. An AMRESORTS mark may be used in conjunction with links, schedules, product descriptions, or order forms, expressly referring to the sale of AMRESORTS travel products by the agency. c. In any case where the AMRESORTS name or mark is used, the name of the travel agency must appear on the same screen, above the AMRESORTS name or mark, and in a size at least 125% of the size of the AMRESORTS name or mark used.

### Print Advertising 

No AMRESORTS marks may appear in Yellow Pages advertising.  
As discussed above, truthful, informational statements are permitted in promotional materials and advertisements, such as, "We sell AMRESORTS travel packages." In any case where the AMRESORTS name or mark is used, the name of the travel agency must appear in close proximity, above the AMRESORTS name or mark, and in a size at least 125% of the size of the AMRESORTS name or mark used.

Marks must not be used as an agency identifier; i.e., an AMRESORTS mark may not appear by itself or at the top of a page in an advertisement.

### Our Contact Information 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [webmaster@AMRESORTS.com](mailto:webmaster@amresorts.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please write to AMRESORTS, 7 Campus Blvd, Newtown Square, PA 19073, Attn: Web Department.
